A Guide to the Annie McDonald Hale Sheet Music Collection, 1892-1987
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- R (Box-folder 2-8)
  - "Red Sails in the Sunset" - words by Jimmy Kennedy; music by Hugh Williams (New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Company) 1935
  - "Remember Pearl Harbor" - words by Don Reid; music by Don Reid and Sammy Kaye (New York: Republic Music) 1941
  - "A Rendezvous With a Dream" [incomplete] - words and music by Leo Robin and Ralph Rainger (New York: Famous Music) [1936]
  - "Richard and His Sweetheart Nell" - words by Carl Bruche; music by W. F. Sudds (South Bend, IN: Studebaker Bros.) 1892
  - "Riders in the Sky (A Cowboy Legend)" - words and music by Stan Jones (New York: Edwin H. Morris & Company) 1949
  - "Rose O'Day (The Filla-Ga-Dusha Song)" - words and music by Charlie Tobias and Al Lewis (New York: Tobias and Lewis) 1941
- Sa - Sl (Box-folder 2-9)
  - "St. Louis Tickle" - music by Barney and Seymour (Chicago: Victor Kremer) 1904
  - "Selections from The Sound of Music" - words by Oscar Hammerstein II; music by Richard Rodgers (New York: Williamson Music) 1960
  - "Sentimental Journey" - words and music by Bud Green, Les Brown, Ben Homer (New York: Edwin H. Morris) 1945
  - "Shenandoah" folk song; piano solo arranged by Jack Butler (Cincinnati, OH: Willis Music) 1965
  - "Shenandoah (Across the Wide Missouri)" - arranged by Stephen Sechak (New York: Larrabee) 1963
  - "Shepherd Serenade" - words by Kermit Goell; music by Fred Spielman (New York: Mayfair Music) 1941
  - "The Shrine of St. Cecilia" - words by Carroll Loveday; music by Jokern (New York: Braun Music) 1941
- Sm - Sn (Box-folder 2-10)
  - "Smiles" - words by J. Will Callahan; music by Lee S. Roberts (Detroit: Jerome H. Remick) 1918
  - "Smiles of Silver and Kisses of Gold" - words and music by Kendis, Brockman, Vincent (New York: Kendis-Brockman Music) 1919
  - "Snookey Ookums" - words and music by Irving Berlin (New York: Waterson, Berlin & Snyder) 1913
- So (Box-folder 2-11)
  - "Some Girls Do and Some Girls Don't" - words and music by Howard Johnson, Alex Gerber, Harry Jentes (New York: Leo. Feist) 1916
  - "Some Sunday Morning" - words by Ted Koehler; music by M. K. Jerome and Ray Heindorf (New York: Harms) 1945
  - "Somebody Stole My Gal" - words and music by Leo Wood (New York: Meyer Cohen Music) 1918
  - "Somewhere in France is Daddy" - words and music by The Great Howard (New York: Plaza Music) 1917
  - "The Sound of Music" - words by Oscar Hammerstein II; music by Richard Rodgers (New York: Williamson Music) 1959
  - "South America, Take It Away!" - words and music by Harold Rome (New York: M. Witmark & Sons) 1946
  - "South American Way" - words by Al Dubin; music by Jimmy McHugh (New York: Harms) 1939
  - "South of the Border" - words and music by Jimmy Kennedy and Michael Carr (New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Company) 1939
- Sp - Sz (Box-folder 2-12)
  - "Star Dust" - words by Mitchell Parish; music by Hoagy Carmichael (New York: Mills Music) 1929
  - "Stingy Kid" - words by Alfred Bryan; music by Nat Goldstein (New York: Jerome H. Remick) 1909
  - "Stop Beatin' 'Round the Mulberry Bush" - words by Bickley Reichner; music by Clay Boland (New York: Bregman, Vocco and Conn) 1938
  - "Strike Up the Band" - words by Ira Gershwin; music by George Gershwin (New York: New World Music) 1940
  - "Summer Time (Lullaby)" - words by Du Bose Heyward; music by George Gershwin (New York: Gershwin) 1935
  - "Surrender" - words and music by Bennie Benjamin and George Weiss (New York: Santly-Joy) 1946
  - "Swinging on a Star" [incomplete] - words by Johnny Burke; music by Jimmy Van Heusen (New York: Burke and Van Heusen) [1939?]
  - "Symphony" - words by Andre Tabét and Roger Bernstein (American version by Jack Lawrence); music by Alstone (New York: Chappell) 1945
- Ta - Tn (Box-folder 2-13)
  - "A Taste of Honey" - words by Ric Marlow; music by Bobby Scott (New York: Songfest Music) 1962
  - "Temptation" - words by Louis Weslyn; music by Henry Lodge (New York: M. Witmark & Sons) 1909
  - "That's My Desire" - words by Carroll Loveday; music by Helmy Kresa (New York: Mills Music) 1947
  - "There Goes That Song Again" - words by Sammy Cahn; music by Jule Styne (New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Company) 1944
  - "There'll Be Blue Birds Over the White Cliffs of Dover" - words by Nat Burton; music by Walter Kent (New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Company) 1941, [2 copies; alternate covers]
  - "A-Tisket, A-Tasket" - words and music by Ella Fitzgerald and Al Feldman (New York: Robbins Music) 1938
- To - Tz (Box-folder 2-14)
  - "To Each His Own" - words and music by Jay Livingston and Ray Evans (New York: Paramount Music) 1946
  - "Too-Ra-Loo-Ra-Loo-Ral That's an Irish Lullaby" - words and music by J. R. Shannon (New York: M. Witmark & Sons) 1944
  - "The Trail of the Lonesome Pine" - words by Ballard Macdonald; music by Harry Carroll (New York: Shapiro, Bernstein & Company) 1913
  - "Tonight" - words by Stephen Sondheim; music by Leonard Bernstein (New York: G. Schirmer) 1957
  - "A Trip to Niagara" - music by Wm. J. Cornish (New York: Will Wood) 1904
  - "Twenty-four Hours of Sunshine" - words by Carl Sigman; music by Peter De Rose (New York: Advanced Music) 1949
  - "Twilight in Sleepy Hollow" - by Vernon Lane (Philadelphia: Theodore Presser) 1940
- U - V (Box-folder 2-15)
  - "Underneath the Japanese Moon" - words by Gene Buck; music by W. Gus. Haenschen (New York: T. B. Harms & Francis Day & Hunter) 1914
  - "Vaya Con Dios (May God Be With You)" - words and music by Larry Russell, Inez James and Buddy Pepper (New York: Ardmore Music) 1953
- Wa - Wg (Box-folder 2-16)
  - "Wait for Me Mary" - words and music by Charlie Tobias, Nat Simon, Harry Tobias (New York: Remick Music) 1942
  - "Waitin' for the Train to Come In" - words and music by Sunny Skylar and Martin Block (New York: Martin Block Music) 1945
  - "Wake the Town and Tell the People" - words by Sammy Gallop; music by Jay Livingston (New York: Joy Music) 1955
  - "We're Going Over" - words and music by Andrew B. Sterling, Bernie Grossman, Arthur Lange (New York: Joe Morris Music) 1917
- Wh (Box-folder 2-17)
  - "What I Did for Love" - words by Edward Kleban; music by Marvin Hamlisch (Miami Beach, FL: Hansen House) c1975
  - "When the Lights Go On Again (All Over the World)" - words and music by Eddie Seiler, Sol Marcus, Bennie Benjemen (New York: Campbell, Loft and Porgie) 1942
  - "When the Saints Go Marching In" - traditional; words and music adapted by Jay Arnold (New York: Larrabee) 1963
  - "When You Wore a Tulip and I Wore a Big Red Rose" [incomplete] - words by Jack Mahoney; music by Percy Wenrich (New York: Leo. Feist) 1914
  - "When Your Heart's on Fire, Smoke Gets in Your Eyes" - words by Otto Harbach; music by Jerome Kern (New York: T. B. Harms) 1933
  - "Who Are You With To-night?" - words by Harry Williams; music by Egbert Van Alstyne (New York: Jerome H. Remick) 1910
  - "Who Will Buy" - words and music by Lionel Bart (London: Lakeview Music) 1968
  - "The Whole World Is Singing My Song" - words by Mann Curtis; music by Vic Mizzy (New York: Robbins Music) 1946
  - "Why Was I Ever Born Lazy" - words by Billy Devere; music by Dawson Wood (New York: H. J. Wood) 1907
- Wi - Wz (Box-folder 2-18)
  - "Winter Moon" - words by W. Amos Thompson; music by Frank J. Allen (Detroit: Jerome H. Remick) 1911
  - "Without a Song" - words by William Rose and Edward Eliscu; music by Vincent Youmans (New York: Miller Music) 1929
  - "Wouldn't It Be Loverly" - words by Alan Jay Lerner; music by Frederick Loewe (New York: Chappell) 1956
- Y - Z (Box-folder 2-19)
  - "Yellow Bird" - words and music by Norman Luboff, Marilyn Keith, Alan Bergman (New York: Frank Music) 1958
  - "Yellow Submarine" - words and music by John Lennon and Paul McCartney (New York: Maclen Music) 1966
  - "Yes! We Have No Bananas" - words and music by Frank Silver and Irving Cohn (New York: Skidmore Music) 1923
  - "You Don't Loaf Heah No Mo'" - words and music by Cecil Mann (New York: Old Dominion Music) 1904
  - "You'll Never Know" - words by Mack Gordon; music by Harry Warren (New York: Bregman, Vocco & Conn) 1943
  - "You'll Never Walk Alone" - words by Oscar Hammerstein II; music by Richard Rodgers (New York: Williamson Music) 1945
  - "You've Got Me Goin' Kid" - words by R. H. Cochrane; music by P. D. Cochrane (Chicago: Music House of Laemmle) 1909
  - "You've Got to See Mamma Ev'ry Night (Or You Can't See Mamma At All)" - words and music by Billy Rose and Con Conrad (New York: Leo. Feist) 1923